tutoriallounge.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Tutorial Lounge | Tutorial Lounge

When you reached TutorialLounge.com, the privacy of our respected visitors is of great importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by TutorialLounge.com and how it is used.

### Logbook Files

As you know many other websites making log files and we also following same process at TutorialLounge.com, The Inside info as log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date / time stamp, referring / exit pages, browser type of language, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Email addresses are only provided by the user voluntarily through the commenting process or via e-mail communications. Authors’ personal information collected through 3rd party forms are also provided voluntarily and will remain confidential and abide by the terms stated in this privacy policy.

### Cookies And Web Beacons

TutorialLounge.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TutorialLounge.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to TutorialLounge.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the

following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: [Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense)  and [Amazon](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on TutorialLounge.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

TutorialLounge.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You can however opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies. In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies to collect personal information and help personalize your online experience.

### Advertisements

TutorialLounge.com including any predecessor or affiliated companies, does not signify or ratify the accuracy or reliability of any of the advertisements (collectively), i.e. links, banners, downloads, distributions or other information accessed directly or indirectly from host advertisements contained on this website (Service), nor the quality of any products, information or other materials displayed, purchased or obtained by any consumer, as a result of an advertisement or any other information or offer in connection with the service or products.

TutorialLounge.com shall not be responsible for any errors or oversights contained within any 3rd party advertisements contained within its website, and reserve the right to make changes and adjust content without notice. Therefore, TutorialLounge.com and 3rd party information are provided “AS IS.” You, the consumer, acknowledge that any reliance upon any materials shall be at your sole risk.

3rd party advertisers featured on TutorialLounge.com may collect tracking information in a different manner than is set out in this Privacy Policy. The only information that they will be able to track is basic website usage information and other analytic.
